Guide to the Victor S. Navasky Papers TAM.594
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series IV: The Hollywood Blacklist and Naming Names, 1935-2013
  - Subseries IVA: Research and Related Materials
    - Blankfort, Michael (includes interview transcript), 1951-1952, undated (Box 19, Folder 42)
    - Bloomgarden, Kermit, 1976, undated (Box 19, Folder 43)
    - "Body and Soul" (sports film), 1975 (Box 19, Folder 44)
    - Bok, Sissela: Notes concerning her book on lying, undated (Box 19, Folder 45)
    - Bontecou, Eleanor: Photocopies of selections from her papers at the Truman Presidential Library, undated (Box 19, Folder 46-47)
    - Boorstin, Daniel, 1977-1978 (Box 19, Folder 48)
    - Bosworth, Patricia, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 49)
    - Boudin, Leonard, undated (Box 19, Folder 50)
    - Boveri, Margaret, undated (Box 19, Folder 51)
    - Brand, Millen, undated (Box 19, Folder 52)
    - Brecht, Bertolt, 1974, undated (Box 19, Folder 53)
    - Brewer, Roy, 1953-1954, 1962, undated (Box 19, Folder 54)
    - Bridges, Lloyd, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 55)
    - Bright, John, undated (Box 19, Folder 56)
    - Broidy, Steve, undated (Box 19, Folder 57)
    - Bromberg, Conrad, 1973, 1975, undated (Box 19, Folder 58)
    - Browder, Earl, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 59)
    - Brown, Phil, 1973, undated (Box 19, Folder 60)
    - Browne, Corinne, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 61)
    - Brumberg, Abraham, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Buchanan, Cynthia (includes copies of correspondence with Arthur Miller), 1976 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Buchman, Beatrice, 1975, undated (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Budenz, Louis F., 1950-1951 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Burnham, James, undated (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Burrows, Abe, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - California: Trips, 1972-1975, undated (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Calomiris, Angela: Notes from Red Masquerade, undated (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Cameron, Angus (includes several documents re: the Matusow Case), 1953, 1955, undated (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Caspary, Vera, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Caute, David, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Cenedella, Robert, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Censorship, blacklisting (originals), Feb 1960-Apr 1960 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Censorship, blacklisting (photocopies), Feb 1960-Apr 1960 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Chafee, Zechariah, Jr., 1952 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Chambers, Whittaker: Notes from Witness, undated (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Chase, Stanley, undated (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Choporov, Ed, undated (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Chronology, undated (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - Churchill, Mae, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - Claiborne, Robert: "My Years on the Blacklist", 1976 (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - Clearance/ "Rehabilitation" material, 1952-1953, 1960, undated (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - Clurman, Harold, 1979, undated (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - Cobb, Lee J., 1976, undated (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - Cobb, Lee J.: FBI file, 1947-1979 (Box 20, Folder 25)
    - Cochran, Bert (includes Labor and Communism: The Conflict That Shaped American Unions), 1978 (Box 20, Folder 26)
    - The Cocktail Party (T.S. Eliot): Notes, undated (Box 20, Folder 27)
    - Cogley Report ("Report on Blacklisting"), 1955-1957, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 28)
    - Cohen, Phil, 1982, undated (Box 20, Folder 29)
    - Cohn, Roy, 1957-1968 (Box 20, Folder 30)
    - Cohn, Roy (includes documents from USA v. Roy M. Cohn and Murray E. Gottesman), 1963 (Box 20, Folder 31)
    - Cohn, Roy (original newspaper clippings), 1957-1965 (Box 20, Folder 32)
    - Cohn, Sidney, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 33)
    - Cold War, undated (Box 20, Folder 34)
    - Cole, Lester, 1973, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 35)
    - Communist Party USA, 1976, undated (Box 20, Folder 36)
    - Concentration Camp Bill, 1971, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 37)
    - Cook, Bruce (re: Dalton Trumbo), undated (Box 20, Folder 38)
    - Coplon Case (photocopy of article "Film Communists listed in FBI File in Coplon Spy Case"), 1949 (Box 20, Folder 39)
    - Correspondence, 1972-1981 (Box 20, Folder 40)
    - Counterattack, 1950, 1952, undated (Box 20, Folder 41)
    - Crouch, Paul (includes material re: Clifford Durr), 1977-1978 (Box 20, Folder 42)
    - Daggett, Charles: Letter describing his experience at the Hollywood hearings, undated (Box 20, Folder 43)
    - Dare, Danny, 1953 (Box 20, Folder 44)
    - Daube, David, undated (Box 20, Folder 45)
    - David, Robert Gorham, 1976, undated (Box 20, Folder 46)
    - Davis, Sidney, 1976, undated (Box 20, Folder 47)
    - Democratic Record Against Communism in America (Factsheet, Democratic National Committee), 1953 (Box 20, Folder 48)
    - Demster, Curt, undated (Box 20, Folder 49)
    - Deutscher, Isaac, undated (Box 20, Folder 50)
    - Diamond, Sigmund (and McGeorge Bundy), 1977, undated (Box 20, Folder 51)
    - Dickson (folk), undated (Box 20, Folder 52)
    - Dickstein, Morris, undated (Box 20, Folder 53)
    - Diggins, John P., 1975 (Box 20, Folder 54)
    - "The Dimensions of Psychological Well-Being: A Critical Review" by Andrew Cherlin and Leo G. Reeder, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 55)
    - DiPierna, Paula, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 56)
    - "The Distorted Prism, Radical Politics and Hollywood, 1930-1960" by Ceplair and Englund: Draft - Intro and Chapters 1 and 2, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 57)
    - "The Distorted Prism, Radical Politics and Hollywood, 1930-1960" by Ceplair and Englund: Draft - Chapters 3 and 4, 1979 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - "The Distorted Prism, Radical Politics and Hollywood, 1930-1960" by Ceplair and Englund: Draft - Chapters 5 and 6, 1979 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - "The Distorted Prism, Radical Politics and Hollywood, 1930-1960" by Ceplair and Englund: Draft - Chapters 7 and 8, 1979 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - "The Distorted Prism, Radical Politics and Hollywood, 1930-1960" by Ceplair and Englund: Draft - Chapters 9 and 10, 1979 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - "The Distorted Prism, Radical Politics and Hollywood, 1930-1960" by Ceplair and Englund: Draft - Chapter 11, 1979 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - "The Distorted Prism, Radical Politics and Hollywood, 1930-1960" by Ceplair and Englund: Draft -Final Sections (afterword, appendices, bibliography), 1979 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - "The Distorted Prism, Radical Politics and Hollywood, 1930-1960" by Ceplair and Englund: Navasky notes, 1979 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Dmytryk, Edward, 1951, undated (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Donner, Frank J.: Correspondence and interview transcript, 1976-1977 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Donner, Frank J.: Notes, undated (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Donner, Frank J.: Writings, 1954, 1971-1975, undated (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Draper, Paul, undated (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Dryden, Harriet, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Duclos letter, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Dunne, Phil, undated (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Dunnock, Mildred, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - D'usseau, Susan, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Edelman, Murray, 1975, undated (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Eliscu, Edward, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - Endore, Guy: "Reflections of Guy Endore", 1964 (Box 21, Folder 20-22)
    - English, Richard (includes article on Edward Dmytryk and description of anti-communist radio series "Last Man Out"), 1951-1954, undated (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - Ephron, Henry, undated (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - Euro-communism, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - "False Consciousness and the Fact/Value Problem": Presentation by Dale E. Hass to the American Political Science Association, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 26)
    - False Witness by Melvin Rader: Introduction to the second edition, undated (Box 21, Folder 27)
    - Fast, Howard, 1948, undated (Box 21, Folder 28)
    - Faulk, John Henry: Fear on Trial, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 29)
    - Festinger, Leon, undated (Box 21, Folder 30)
    - Fiedler, Leslie, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 31)
    - Fifth amendment, 1953, 1973, undated (Box 21, Folder 32)
    - Finn, Pauline, undated (Box 21, Folder 33)
    - Fitelson, William, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 34)
    - Flatley, Guy, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 35)
    - Focus and Themes, undated (Box 21, Folder 36)
    - "Folksingers", undated (Box 21, Folder 37)
    - Foreman, Carl, 1958, 1969, 1976, undated (Box 21, Folder 38)
    - Foreman, Estelle, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 39)
    - Forster, Arnold, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Forster, E.M.: "What I Believe", undated (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Fortas, Abe, 1952 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Fox, John: "The Reasons for the Red Scare", 1977 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - France, Royal W., undated (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Frank, Waldo, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Franklin, Ray, undated (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Freeman, Joseph, undated (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Freeman, Y. Frank (also re: Joe Sistrom), 1952, undated (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Freed, Judy, 1972, undated (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Freedman, Monroe, undated (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Friedman (Leon) and Dorsen (Norman), 1978, undated (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Friedrich, Carl J., undated (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Friendly, Alfred (includes photocopies of selected articles from Washington Post series re: Americans Who Left the US "During the Red Hunt"), 1971-1973 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Fry, undated (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Fund for the Republic: "Editorial Comments on John Cogley's 'Report on Blacklisting'", circa 1956 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Fund for the Republic (from Paul Jacobs): Focus on John Cogley's "Report on Blacklisting", 1955-1956, 1969, undated (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Fund for the Republic: Letter (Mar 1, 1956) from American Committee for Cultural Freedom, Inc. (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - Fund for the Republic: Reprint of "Legal Aspects of 'Political Black Listing' in the Entertainment Industry" by Harold W. Horowitz, 1956 (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - Gang, Martin, 1951-1976, undated (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - Gang, Martin, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - Gang, Martin (also includes American Jewish Committee): Correspondence and other Documents (Research for Chapter 5 "The Collaborators"), 1947-1953, 1964 (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - Gang, Martin (also includes American Jewish Committee: Correspondence and other Documents (Research for Chapter 5 "The Collaborators"), 1950-1958, 1964 (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - Gang, Martin: Notes, undated (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - Garfinkel, Harold, 1976, undated (Box 22, Folder 25)
    - Gelman, Milton, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 26)
    - Gersh, Phil, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 27)
    - Gilbert, Lou, undated (Box 22, Folder 28)
    - Gillmoor, Dan, undated (Box 22, Folder 29)
    - Ginness, Abe, undated (Box 22, Folder 30)
    - Goffman, Erving, undated (Box 22, Folder 31)
    - Goldburg, Bob, undated (Box 22, Folder 32)
    - Goldstein, Abe, undated (Box 22, Folder 33)
    - Gollobin, Ira, undated (Box 22, Folder 34)
    - Goodman, Water, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 35)
    - Gordon, Michael, 1975, undated (Box 22, Folder 36)
    - Goyen, William, 1972, undated (Box 22, Folder 37)
    - Grant, Lee, undated (Box 22, Folder 38)
    - Green, Gil, undated (Box 22, Folder 39)
    - Grodzins, Morton, undated (Box 22, Folder 40)
    - Grosbard, Ulu, undated (Box 22, Folder 41)
    - Group Theater, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 42)
    - Guilt, undated (Box 22, Folder 43)
    - Gusfield, Joseph R.: "Moral Passage: The Symbolic Process in Public Designations of Deviance", undated (Box 22, Folder 44)
    - Gussow, Mel, undated (Box 22, Folder 45)
    - Harburg, Yip, 1950-1953, undated (Box 22, Folder 46)
    - Harding, John, undated (Box 22, Folder 47)
    - Harper, Alan D.: Notes from The Politics of Loyalty: The White House and the Communist Issue, 1946-1962, undated (Box 22, Folder 48)
    - Harrington, Michael, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 49)
    - Harris, Richard: "Taking the Fifth-II", 1976 (Box 22, Folder 50)
    - Hasuike, Reiko, 1977 (Box 22, Folder 51)
    - Hayden, Sterling, 1951, undated (Box 22, Folder 52)
    - Hecht, Harold, undated (Box 22, Folder 53)
    - Heitler, Susan E.: "A Presentation for a Feature Documentary on Several Men and Women Whose Lives Were Altered Dramatically and Irrevocably by the House Un-American Activities Committee", 1976 (Box 22, Folder 54)
    - Heller, Diana: "Informing in Jewish Law" (paper, New York Law School), 1977 (Box 22, Folder 55)
    - Hellman, Lillian, 1965, 1975-1977, undated (Box 22, Folder 56)
    - Hellman, Lillian, undated (Box 22, Folder 57)
    - Helpern, David, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 58)
    - Heym, Stefan, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 59)
    - Heyman, Harriet, undated (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Hicks, Granville, 1953 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Hodges, Donald Clark: "Ethics and Manners" (notes), undated (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Holbrook, Hal: Letter to Navasky, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Holliday, Judy, 1951, 1953, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Hollywood on Trial (Film directed by David Helpern): Notes, undated (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Hollywood Reds: Newspaper clippings (originals), 1950-1953, 1966, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Hollywood Reds: Newspaper clippings (originals), undated (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Hollywood Reds: Newspaper clippings (photocopies), 1950-1953, 1966, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Hollywood Reds: Newspaper clippings (photocopies), undated (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - The Hollywood Reporter and Daily Variety: Notes, undated (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Hollywood Ten, 1957, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - "The Hollywood Writers' Wars" by Nancy Lynn Schwartz (uncorrected proof), 1951 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Hook, Sidney, 1974-1977, undated (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Hoover, J. Edgar (photocopies of selected correspondence), 1945-1951 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Horowitz, Irving, 1977, undated (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - House Un-American Activities Committee (HJAC): Articles, testimonies, reports, 1957-1959, 1967-1972 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Howe, Irving, undated (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Huebsch, Edward, undated (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Hughes, Everett C., undated (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - Hughes, Langston, 1953, 1974-1975 (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - "The Human Costs of the Cold War, Dialogue in Alabama": Transcript of workshop led by Jack O'Dell, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - Hynes, Sam, undated (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - Images of Communism, undated (Box 23, Folder 24)
    - Individuals (includes "Who Identified" and "Names Named"), undated (Box 23, Folder 25)
    - Informer: Various articles and quotes, 1955, 1970-1977, undated (Box 23, Folder 26)
    - The Intellectuals and McCarthy: The Radical Specter by Michael Paul Rogin, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 27)
    - Interview Notes (notebooks): Various, undated (Box 23, Folder 28)
    - Jacobs, Paul, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 29)
    - Jacobson, Mark, undated (Box 23, Folder 30)
    - Jaffe, Sam, undated (Box 23, Folder 31)
    - Jarrico, Paul, 1952, 1955, undated (Box 23, Folder 32)
    - Jarrico, Sylvia, undated (Box 23, Folder 33)
    - Jelagin, [Uri], undated (Box 23, Folder 34)
    - Jerome, Victor J. (photocopies of materials from Yale University Library, 1940s-1960s), 1976 (Box 23, Folder 35)
    - Jews and Communism, undated (Box 23, Folder 36)
    - Kael, Pauline (film reviews), 1973, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 37)
    - Kahane, B.B., 1954, 1961 (Box 23, Folder 38)
    - Kahn, Albert E., undated (Box 23, Folder 39)
    - Kahn, Gordon, undated (Box 23, Folder 40)
    - Kanfer, Stephan, 1972, undated (Box 23, Folder 41)
    - Kaplan, Leon, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 42)
    - Katz, Charles, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 43)
    - Kaufman, Irving R., 1975 (Box 23, Folder 44)
    - Kazan, Elia, 1947-1972, undated (Box 23, Folder 45)
    - Kazan, Elia, 1972-1973, undated (Box 23, Folder 46)
    - Kazan, Elia: Bibliography, undated (Box 23, Folder 47)
    - Kazan, Elia: Correspondence, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 48)
    - Kazan, Elia: Dimitroff, undated (Box 23, Folder 49)
    - Kazan, Elia: "Elia Kazan and the House Un-American Activities Committee" by Roger Tailleur, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 50)
    - Kazan, Elia: magazine issue devoted to articles re: Kazan, 1972 (Box 23, Folder 51)
    - Kazan, Elia: News clippings, 1952-1978 (Box 23, Folder 52)
    - Kazan, Elia: On the Waterfront, 1973, undated (Box 23, Folder 53)
    - Kazan, Elia: Photographs, 1935-1962, undated (Box 23, Folder 54)
    - Kazan, Elia:Wesleyan University (appraisal of Kazan materials at Wesleyan and 1971 talk at Wesleyan), 1968, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Kazin, Alfred, undated (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Kempton, Murray, 1951-1956, 1964, undated (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Kenny, Robert, undated (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Kerby, Elizabeth, undated (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Kibbee, Roland, 1975 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Kimple, William Ward, 1955, undated (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - King, Alan, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Kinoy, Ernest (re: Television program: Blacklist), 1964 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Kluger, Richard: Review of The Great Fear: The Anti-Communist Purge Under Truman and Eisenhower by David Caute, undated (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Knowles, Clayton, undated (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Koch, Howard, 1973, undated (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Koestler, Arthur, undated (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Kopelev, Lev: Review of his book To Be Preserved Forever (review written by Arthur Miller), 1977 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Kovell, Joel, undated (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Kraber, Tony, Dec 1950, 1953-1955, 1973, undated (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Kraber, Tony (includes Navasky's notes), May 1952, Aug 1955, Mar 1973, undated (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - Kraber, Tony: Newspaper clippings (originals), 1951-1953, undated (Box 24, Folder 18-19)
    - Kraber, Tony: Newspaper clippings (photocopies), 1951-1953 (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - Kraber, Tony: Newspaper clippings (photocopies), 1955 (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - Kraber, Tony: Newspaper clippings (photocopies), undated (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - Kraber, Tony: Red Channels, Jun 1950, Dec 1951 (Box 24, Folder 23)
    - Kraft, Hyman: Notes from On My Way to the Theater, undated (Box 24, Folder 24)
    - Kramer, Hilton, 1976-1977 (Box 24, Folder 25)
    - Kravchenko, Victor, undated (Box 24, Folder 26)
    - Kristol, Irving, 1952, undated (Box 24, Folder 27)
    - Kunen, James S., undated (Box 24, Folder 28)
    - Lahn, Ilse, 1976 (Box 24, Folder 29)
    - Lampell, Millard, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 30)
    - Lang, David A., undated (Box 24, Folder 31)
    - Langer, Elinor, 1974 (Box 24, Folder 32)
    - Lardner, Ring Jr., 1948, 1974-1977, undated (Box 24, Folder 33)
    - The Last Tycoon, 1976 (Box 24, Folder 34)
    - Lastfogel, Abe, undated (Box 24, Folder 35)
    - Lattimore, Owen, undated (Box 24, Folder 36)
    - Lawrence, Marc, undated (Box 24, Folder 37)
    - Lawson, John Howard, 1965, 1972-1977, undated (Box 24, Folder 38)
    - Lawson, John Howard, undated (Box 24, Folder 39)
    - Lawson, John Howard: Inventory of papers at Southern Illinois University, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 40)
    - Lawyers, undated (Box 24, Folder 41)
    - Lee, Canada, 1952, undated (Box 24, Folder 42)
    - Lennart, Isobel, undated (Box 24, Folder 43)
    - Leonard, John, 1970-1977 (Box 24, Folder 44)
    - Levin, Mayer, 1952, 1974, undated (Box 24, Folder 45)
    - Levinson, [Sanford]: Course materials for Politics 306, "The Politics of Civil Liberties", 1977 (Box 24, Folder 46)
    - Levinson, Suzanne, 1976 (Box 24, Folder 47)
    - Levitt, Helen and Al, 1951, 1976, undated (Box 24, Folder 48)
    - Levy, Mel, 1970, undated (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Lewis, Anthony, undated (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - "Liberal Values, The Cold War, and American Intellectuals: The Trauma of the Alger Hiss Case" by Kenneth O'Reilly, undated (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Liberty - NBC News Special: Transcript, 1976 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Libraries (correspondence concerning research visits to various libraries), 1975-1976 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Liebowitz, Ellen: Research concerning entertainment unions' policies towards allegedly subversive activities in the 1940s-1950s, 1976, undated (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Lifton, Robert, undated (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Lincoln Center (Lincoln Center Repertory) including articles on After The Fall (re: Miller and Kazan), 1964, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Loden, Barbaro, undated (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - London Interviews, 1973, undated (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Losey, Joseph, 1964-1975, undated (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Lourie, Jerry, undated (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Low, Richard, undated (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Lytton, Bart, undated (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Maddow, Ben, undated (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - Maltz, Albert, 1970, undated (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - Maltz, Albert: Articles and news clippings, 1950-1952, 1967, 1973-1977 (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - Maltz, Albert: The Citizen Writer, 1950 (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - Maltz, Albert: Correspondence, 1946-1951, 1976 (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - Maltz, Albert: Correspondence - Copies of letters between Maltz and Dalton Trumbo, Maltz and Ring Lardner Jr., 1972-1973, 1977 (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - Maltz, Albert: Correspondence - Copies of Maltz-lawyer letters, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - Maltz, Albert: Notes, undated (Box 25, Folder 22)
    - Maltz, Albert: Transcripts, 1972-1976 (Box 25, Folder 23)
    - Mancini, Pat, 1975-1976 (Box 25, Folder 24)
    - Mandel, Lou, undated (Box 25, Folder 25)
    - March, Frederick Mrs., undated (Box 25, Folder 26)
    - Margolis, Ben, 1950, 1960, undated (Box 25, Folder 27)
    - Marker, Jeffrey Martin, 1976, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 28)
    - Marshall, William, 1975, undated (Box 25, Folder 29)
    - Mark, Gary T., undated (Box 25, Folder 30)
    - Marzani, Carl, 1947, 1972, undated (Box 25, Folder 31)
    - May, Lary Linden: "Patriotism in Early Hollywood: A Comment on the Political Culture of Red Scares, 1918-1921", 1977 (Box 25, Folder 32)
    - Matusow, Harvey, 1972, undated (Box 25, Folder 33)
    - Mayer, Arno, undated (Box 25, Folder 34)
    - McAuliffe [Mary S.] and the ACLU, undated (Box 25, Folder 35)
    - McCarthy, Joseph, 1973-1977 (Box 25, Folder 36)
    - McCarthy, Mary: "Naming Names, The Arthur Miller Case", 1957 (Box 25, Folder 37)
    - McClosky, Herbert, 1965, 1970, undated (Box 25, Folder 38)
    - McWilliams, Carey, 1952, 1973-1977, undated (Box 25, Folder 39)
    - Milgram, Stanley, 1977 (Box 25, Folder 40)
    - Miller, Arthur: After The Fall, 1964 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Miller, Arthur: Articles (photocopies) with Navasky annotations, 1953, 1960s (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Miller, Arthur: Articles (photocopies) with Navasky annotations, 1960s (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Miller, Arthur: Articles (photocopies) with Navasky annotations, 1970s (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Miller, Arthur: Correspondence and interview, 1972, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Miller, Arthur: The Creation of the World and Other Businesses, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Miller, Arthur: The Crucible, 1972, undated (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Miller, Arthur: Incident at Vichy, undated (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Miller, Arthur: University of Texas notes, 1972, undated (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Miller, Arthur: View From the Bridge, 1965, undated (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Miller, Arthur: "The Year it Came Apart" by Arthur Miller (with Navasky notes) - New York Magazine issue re: the year 1949, Dec 30, 1974; Jan 6, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Miller, Arthur: Youth Board, 1955 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Miller, Arthur and Elia Kazan: Articles (photocopies) with Navasky annotations, 1935-1970s (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Miller, Arthur and Elia Kazan: Articles (photocopies) with Navasky annotations, 1950s-1970s (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Miller, Merle: "Is There a Blacklist?", 1952 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Mitford, Jessica, undated (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - Mitgang [Herbert], undated (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - Monroe, Marilyn: Includes "The Strange Death of Marilyn Monroe" by Frank A. Capell, 1964, 2011, undated (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - Moore, Barrington, undated (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - Moore, Sam, undated (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - Mostel, Zero, 1974, undated (Box 26, Folder 21)